A Guide to the Records of the Secretary of the Commonwealth, Extradition Requisition and Rendition Files of Governor Robert F. McDonnell, 2010-2013
Library of Virginia
Library of Virginia
Records of the Secretary of the Commonwealth, Extradition Requisition and Rendition Files of Governor Robert F. McDonnell, 2010-2013
The Library of Virginia
51137
15 cu. ft.(15 boxes)
Virginia. Secretary of the Commonwealth.
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
The records must be reviewed by staff for privacy protected information before serving. Extradition requisition and rendition letters from the Governor(s) may be served, however records including privacy protected information such as social security numbers may not. Privacy protected and confidential information is restricted from public access for 75 years per code of Virginia 42.1-78, 2.2-3800 and 2.2-3705.1-8. Restricted records were not removed from the collection. Types of information and records may include, but are not limited to: social security numbers, Department of Corrections inmate material, fingerprint files, mediation and settlement discussions, and attorney-client privileged material.
Acquisition Information
Stacy Whitehouse, Office of the Secretary of the Commonwealth, Patrick Henry Building, 1111 East Broad Street, Richmond, VA 23219, transferred 9 January 2014.
Biographical/Historical Information
The Office of the Secretary of the Commonwealth evolved from the yearly Secretary of the Colony. Early Secretaries were elected by the public. An Act of the General Assembly in 1920 changed the election to a joint vote of the General Assembly. In a 1930 Act the duties of the Secretary were redefined with the Secretary of the Commonwealth serving as the ex officio secretary of the Governor, as custodian of many official State records, and as keeper of the Greater and Lesser Seals of the Commonwealth. The office of the Secretary has gradually acquired other functions, such as: service of out-of-state civil process; appointment and regulation of notaries public; and registration and oversight of lobbyists. The Office became a gubernatorial appointment subsequent to a 1958 Act of the Assembly. The Secretary of the Commonwealth is under the jurisdiction of the Governor's Office.
In Virginia, the provisions governing extradition procedures are set forth in Sections 19.2-84 through 19.2-118 of the Code of Virginia. Requisitions and extraditions are handled by the Secretary of the Commonwealth.
Extradition is the legal surrender of an alleged criminal, apprehended in one jurisdiction, to another state, country or other government unit for trial. The accused can be extradited when he or she is charged with any punishable offense in the demanding jurisdiction. Extraditions are both received and requested by the governor. A requisition warrant documents Virginia's request of another state to return a fugitive to Virginia's jurisdiction. A rendition documents another state's request of Virginia to return a fugitive to the requesting state's jurisdiction.
Scope and Content
A typical requisition file contains an application from the Commonwealth's Attorney, a formal request by the Governor for extradition, and the Governor's request of one or more law enforcement officers to retrieve the fugitive. The Commonwealth's Attorney's application usually includes: copies of the indictment or arrest warrant with supporting affidavits and a statement of facts in support of a Governor's Warrant. Some files include a photograph of the subject of the requisition.
A typical rendition file contains a formal request for extradition from another state's governor, correspondence from the Office of the Attorney General to the Office of the Governor concerning the extradition request, and a copy of the notice of extradition sent by the Secretary of the Commonwealth to the wanted individual. The request for extradition usually includes: copies of the indictment or arrest warrant with supporting affidavits and an appointment of agent by the Governor. Some applications may include a photograph of the fugitive. Also included in each files is a Rendition Fact Sheet completed by the Secretary of the Commonwealth. The Rendition Fact Sheet lists date received, jurisdiction, fugitive's name and address, attorney's name and address, date charged as a fugitive, disposition of fugitive warrant, next scheduled court appearance on fugitive warrant, fugitive status (in custody or out on bond), list of pending Virginia charges and disposition and contact information for requestor.
The records from this collection must be reviewed by staff for personal and medical privacy protected information before serving. Both requisitions and renditions may include privacy protected information such as social security and fingerprints, and case, penitentiary, and arrest records.
Arrangement
This collection is arranged into the following series:
Series I: Renditions
Series II: Requisitions
The files are arranged chronologically by year and alphabetically therein.
Contents List
- Series I: Extradition Requisitions and Renditions: Renditions, 2010-2013., Extent: 7 cu. ft. (7 boxes) (Box Boxes 1-4;13-15)
  - Adams, Mykaelynn Daniel, 2010 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Adams, Steven Ross, 2010 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Anderson, Charles Mack Curtis, 2010 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Arnold, Marc James, 2010 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Baez, Tara Ann, 2010 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Baldwin, Richard Lewis, 2010 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Bealle, Teara Latine, 2010 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Blankship, Henry M., 2010 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Boone, Bobby Allen, 2010 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Butler, Darrell, 2010 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Csmp, Walter Claude, 2010 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Csvattaro, Karen Elizabeth, 2010 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Causey, Robert Len, 2010 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Chaklos, Robert Michael, 2010 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Chaydhary, Shahid Aqueel, 2010 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Cochran, Eric Leighton, 2010 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Coleman, Larry Darnell, 2010 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Collins, Kristopher Lawrence, 2010 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Cooper, Marie Angela, 2010 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Crawford, Larenta Omar, 2010 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Crawford, Richard Thomas, Jr., 2010 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Davis, Courtney, 2010 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Dodson, Randall Daniel, 2010 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Edmondson, Frances Ramey, 2010 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Eldert, William Edward, IV, 2010 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Fortner, Randall Berry, 2010 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Freeman, Katrinia Teressa, 2010 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Gaskill, Jessica, 2010 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Haas, John W., 2010 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Halsey, Dennis J., 2010 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Higgins, Christopher D., 2010 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Hilliard, Sabra Kelly, 2010 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Johnson, William J., 2010 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Justice, Glen Dale, 2010 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Justice, Glen Dale, 2010 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Kelly, Allah Truth, 2010 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Kenney, Kimberly Dawn, 2010 (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Kimball, James E., 2010 (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Lake, Robert Scott, 2010 (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Leroyne, Terry, 2010 (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - Mann, Chad Everette, 2010 (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - McDermott, Ryan Paige, 2010 (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - Morris, Gabriel Christian, 2010 (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - Moss, Charity Pauline, 2010 (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - Mullins, David, 2010 (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - Musick, Jeffery Scott, 2010 (Box 1, Folder 46)
  - Newlin, John A., 2010 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Noble, Rusty Lyle, 2010 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Nunez, Dorien, 2010 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Osborne, Evan Darrell, 2010 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Paris, Neal Harding, 2010 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Perry, Ralph Jackson, 2010 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Petroski, Wayne WIlliam, 2010 (1 of 2) (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Petroski, Wayne WIlliam, 2010 (2 of 2) (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Piotrowski, Chris, 2010 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Poe, Earl Frazier, 2010 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Redditt, Louise Toni, 2010 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Ridgeway, Christopher Chad, 2010 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Roman, Felix Garcia, 2010 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Rowell, Leander Bruce, 2010 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Scaperotto, John, 2010 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Smith, Dwayne L., 2010 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Smith, Wesley David, 2010 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Swiney, James Kevin, 2010 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Solano, Pablo, 2010 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Thomas, Deante Sean, 2010 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Torrellas, Francisco Dupreme, 2010 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Torres, Noel Rivera, 2010 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Troup, Robert Allan, 2010 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Ward, Belinda Collier, 2010 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Weldegebbreal, Robel Haddis, 2010 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - White, Christopher Scott, 2010 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Whitelaw, Pierre, 2010 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Whitley, Damien Lee, 2010 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Wilde, Peter Norman, 2010 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Williams, Joel Craig, 2010 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Williams, Malachiah, 2010 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Wyatt, Rhudy Lee Jr., 2010 (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - Wynne, John B., 2010 (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - Addie, Randy, 2011 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Aldridge, Travis Wayne, 2011 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Armstead, Johann Paulette, 2011 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Arnold, Deborah Lynn, 2011 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Arthur, Ricky Lee, 2011 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Battle, Timothy Taron, 2011 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Bell, Keith, 2011 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Blackwell, Garland Ray, Jr., 2011 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Bloomer, Alan Todd, 2011 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Bookwalter, Billy Joe, 2011 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Britt, Anthony Terrell, 2011 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Britton, Judy Anne, 2011 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Brown, Jackie, 2011 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Burns, Patrick, 2011 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Cauley, Eileen Joanne, 2011 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Chapman, Melissa Gail, 2011 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Cochrane, Christopher S., 2011 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Cole, Latoya Nicole, 2011 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Cook, Justin Brandon, 2011 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Couch, Stephen, 2011 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Cromity, Ulysses, 2011 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Davis, William Scott, Jr., 2011 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Dennis, Nathaniel, 2011 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Dickerson, James Edward, 2011 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Doyle, Joseph Frank, 2011 (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Dillon, Kenneth Bobby, 2011 (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Escalante Escobar, Yobani, 2011 (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Frazier, Patrick Michael, 2011 (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - Gattie, Jessica L., 2011 (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - Geiger, Julian D., 2011 (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - Glover, Nathan K., 2011 (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - Graham, Bennie Lee, 2011 (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - Granderson, Carolyn, 2011 (Box 3, Folder 33)
  - Greer, Marlon Dewayne, 2011 (Box 3, Folder 34)
  - Haley, Duane Allen, 2011 (Box 3, Folder 35)
  - Hendrickson, Shayla Lanae, 2011 (Box 3, Folder 36)
  - Hill, Harold, 2011 (Box 3, Folder 37)
  - Hinson, Eugene Allen, 2011 (Box 3, Folder 38)
  - Hobbs, Troy Allen, 2011 (Box 3, Folder 39)
  - Hobbs, Troy Allen, 2011 (Box 3, Folder 40)
  - Holmes, Charles Edward, 2011 (Box 3, Folder 41)
  - Hudson, Malcolm Corenelius, 2011 (Box 3, Folder 42)
  - Hudson, Malcolm Corenelius, 2011 (Box 3, Folder 43)
  - Jacoby, Ernest Jerald, 2011 (Box 3, Folder 44)
  - Jeffries, Charles Joseph, 2011 (Box 3, Folder 45)
  - Jennings, Darryl Keith, 2011 (Box 3, Folder 46)
  - Kerrick, Stephen Monroe, 2011 (Box 3, Folder 47)
  - Kuk, Kyung Soo, 2011 (Box 3, Folder 48)
  - Lester, Neil Brian, 2011 (Box 3, Folder 49)
  - Lewis, Tranetta Danelle, 2011 (Box 3, Folder 50)
  - Marks, Brandon Dale, 2011 (Box 3, Folder 51)
  - Marx, David Hugh, 2011 (Box 3, Folder 52)
  - Maurer, Brandon Aaron, 2011 (Box 3, Folder 53)
  - McCain, Warren J., 2011 (Box 3, Folder 54)
  - McDaniel, William Douglas, 2011 (Box 3, Folder 55)
  - McNair, Dylan Gerard, 2011 (Box 3, Folder 56)
  - Messenger, James David, 2011 (Box 3, Folder 57)
  - Messenger, James Lowell, 2011 (Box 3, Folder 58)
  - Mills, Laurenda Danielle, 2011 (Box 3, Folder 59)
  - Munitz, San Juana, 2011 (Box 3, Folder 60)
  - Nguyen, Quan Ngoc, 2011 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Nunn, Scotty Vanburan, 2011 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Ochoa, Bryan Christopher, 2011 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Ortiz, Benny Allen, 2011 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Pilgram, Allison Brooke, 2011 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Polite, Kristol Lashawn, 2011 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Razo, Alfred Ramirez, 2011 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Reid, Phillip William, 2011 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Reid, Phillip William, 2011 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Ris, Jacqeline Anna, 2011 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Robey, Casey J., 2011 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Robey, Giovanni James, 2011 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Rothmund, Harold J., 2011 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Schatzman, Steve, 2011 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Sheta, Ahmed, 2011 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Shmuckler, Howard D., 2011 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Sims, William L., 2011 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Smith, Marshall Ryan, 2011 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Snow, James Parker, 2011 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Snow, James Parker, 2011 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Stephens, Gwyn Janine, 2011 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Sykes, Shawn W., 2011 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Taylor, Joel J., 2011 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Tipton, Andrea Nicole, 2011 (1 of 2) (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Tipton, Andrea Nicole, 2011 (2 of 2) (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Titus, Jeffrey, 2011 (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Trim, Richard, II, 2011 (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - West, Jermaine Rashard, 2011 (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Wiant, Paul Eugene, 2011 (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Wood, John Lewis, 2011 (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - Woodson, Steven Adam, 2011 (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - Wynne, John B., 2011 (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - Wynne, John B., 2011 (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - Ackerson, Christopher, 2012 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Adamson, Alvin Eugene, 2012 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Artic, Robert Lee, Jr., 2012 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Beezman, Jordan Ryan, 2012 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Birky, Vivian Annette, 2012 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Blakely, Billy Robert, 2012 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Blaise, Miguel A. James, 2012 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Bliss, Lovall Peacen, 2012 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Butler, Anthony D., Sr., 2012 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Carter, Charles Lee, 2012 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Cecilia, Castillo Jose, 2012 (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Charbonnet, Kathryn, 2012 (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - Chavarria, Franklin I., 2012 (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - Cole, Aaron James, 2012 (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - Couch, Rodney Wayne, 2012 (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - Cummings, Tommi Suzannah, 2012 (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - Conner, Ivan David, 2012 (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - Conner, Ivan David, 2012 (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - Cook, Kenneth Ray, 2012 (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - Denise, Abdelwhaid Denis, 2012 (Box 13, Folder 19)
  - Dixon, Quinton Jermaine, 2012 (Box 13, Folder 20)
  - Dobson, David, 2012 (Box 13, Folder 20)
  - Doyle, Kevin Tijuan, 2012 (Box 13, Folder 21)
  - Duncan, Dominic, 2012 (Box 13, Folder 22)
  - Falls, Phalanda D., 2012 (Box 13, Folder 23)
  - Felty, Nora Virginia, 2012 (Box 13, Folder 24)
  - Flannery, Daniel Lee, 2012 (Box 13, Folder 25)
  - Fleming, Christopher Berry, 2012 (Box 13, Folder 26)
  - Foy, Daniel Eugene, 2012 (Box 13, Folder 27)
  - Fox, Dennis Michael, 2012 (Box 13, Folder 28)
  - Frye, Lance Matthew, 2012 (Box 13, Folder 29)
  - Gunnels, James Marvin, 2012 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Guy, Corbett Sherman, 2012 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Guyer, Jeffrey Keith, Sr., 2012 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Hall, David Julius, 2012 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Harden, Eddie James, 2012 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Harper, Nguyen George, 2012 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Harrison, Venus Camille, 2012 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Hatcher, Richard Allen, 2012 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Hayes, Andrew Kelly, 2012 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Hayes, Angelo, 2012 (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Hendry, Lisa Rene, 2012 (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - Hernandez, Antonio, 2012 (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - Hernandez, Oswaldo De Jesus, 2012 (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - Holland, Brian Neill, 2012 (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - Howell, Xavier Allyson, 2012 (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - Hubbard, Steven Anthony, 2012 (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - Jones, Dwayne, 2012 (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - Joppy, Steveland, 2012 (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - Kenesky, Nickolas Thomas, 2012 (Box 14, Folder 18)
  - Kipp, Kenneth E., 2012 (Box 14, Folder 19)
  - Kline, Jeffery Lynn, 2012 (Box 14, Folder 20)
  - Kyle, Eddie, 2012 (Box 14, Folder 21)
  - Lane, Ezekiel, 2012 (Box 14, Folder 22)
  - Lozano, Jose Gomez, 2012 (Box 14, Folder 23)
  - Lynam, James Robert, 2012 (Box 14, Folder 24)
  - McClain, Timothy Eugene, 2012 (Box 14, Folder 25)
  - McCrae, Gerald Martin, II, 2012 (Box 14, Folder 26)
  - McMurray, Ashleigh, 2012 (Box 14, Folder 27)
  - Morrison, James Gerard, III, 2012 (Box 14, Folder 28)
  - Mora-Gonzalez, Terri Lyme, 2012 (Box 14, Folder 29)
  - Nelson, James Brandyn, 2012 (Box 14, Folder 30)
  - Newsome, Zumbotha Ahkiliq, 2012 (Box 14, Folder 31)
  - Parker, James, Jr., 2012 (Box 14, Folder 32)
  - Peacemaker, John Edward, 2012 (Box 14, Folder 33)
  - Peters, Shannon Lynn, 2012 (Box 14, Folder 34)
  - Pope, Elijah Devon, 2012 (Box 14, Folder 35)
  - Pully, William, 2012 (Box 14, Folder 36)
  - Rattler, Alfred Myron, 2012 (Box 14, Folder 37)
  - Rosario, Cristobal Batista, 2012 (Box 14, Folder 38)
  - Rosenbaumd, Samuel Wayne, 2012 (Box 14, Folder 39)
  - Russell, Mark A., 2012 (Box 14, Folder 40)
  - Shewey, James Randolph, 2012 (Box 14, Folder 41)
  - Smith, Edward A., 2012 (Box 14, Folder 42)
  - Smith, Edward A., 2012 (Box 14, Folder 43)
  - Smith, James Glen, 2012 (Box 14, Folder 44)
  - Smith, Jonmarlowe Sterling, 2012 (Box 14, Folder 45)
  - Spencer, Stephanie Marie, 2012 (Box 14, Folder 46)
  - Stanley, Alvin Gamar, 2012 (Box 14, Folder 47)
  - Stanley, Alvin Gamar, 2012 (Box 14, Folder 48)
  - Suggs, Sheri Latia, 2012 (Box 14, Folder 49)
  - Sumter, Sherrell, 2012 (Box 14, Folder 50)
  - Taglianetti, Anthnoy Robert, II, 2012 (Box 14, Folder 51)
  - Taylor, Glenn, Jr., 2012 (Box 14, Folder 52)
  - Taylor, Mondre L., 2012 (Box 14, Folder 53)
  - Thomas, Jacob, 2012 (Box 14, Folder 54)
  - Viers, Gentry Joseph Charles, 2012 (Box 14, Folder 55)
  - Vercruysee, Lauren, 2012 (Box 14, Folder 56)
  - Wales, David Jonathan, 2012 (Box 14, Folder 57)
  - Waters, Tracy Shawn, 2012 (Box 14, Folder 58)
  - Williams, Tony Lee, 2012 (Box 14, Folder 59)
  - Wilson, Donte Edward, 2012 (Box 14, Folder 60)
  - Wilson, William O'neal, 2012 (Box 14, Folder 60)
  - Woolard, Casey Brandon, 2012 (Box 14, Folder 61)
  - Wright, Treva Maude, 2012 (Box 14, Folder 62)
  - Wyatt, Rhudy Lee, 2012 (Box 14, Folder 63)
  - Aklamanu, Yauovi Egno, 2013 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Asuncion, Filemon, 2013 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Atkins, Derek A., 2013 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Cody, Thomas Henry, 2013 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Collins, Anthony Lynn, 2013 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Ellis, Clifford Hampton, 2013 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Gibson, Jennifer Lanice, 2013 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Gomez, Gabriel, 2013 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Guerra, John Armando, 2013 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Hagen, Kevin, 2013 (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Holloway, Monique L., 2013 (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Hylton, Chad Eugene, 2013 (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - Johnson, Joseph Wayne, 2013 (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - Jones, Brady Hugh, 2013 (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - Jones, Lenard, 2013 (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - Jones, Robert Vincent, 2013 (Box 15, Folder 16)
  - Jones, Sharon Lee, 2013 (Box 15, Folder 17)
  - Kelleher, Edward John, 2013 (Box 15, Folder 18)
  - Keller, Rick Allen, 2013 (Box 15, Folder 19)
  - Lambert, Antoine Darnell, 2013 (Box 15, Folder 20)
  - Lee, John Leonard, 2013 (Box 15, Folder 21)
  - Lerchenfeld, Thomas Jeffrey, 2013 (Box 15, Folder 22)
  - Maddox, Richard Garband, Sr., 2013 (Box 15, Folder 23)
  - Mannix, Patrick J., 2013 (Box 15, Folder 24)
  - Martin, Jarrod Nathan, 2013 (Box 15, Folder 25)
  - McCoy, Dwayne J., 2013 (Box 15, Folder 26)
  - McDonald, Brenda J., 2013 (Box 15, Folder 27)
  - McGrath, Patrick M., 2013 (Box 15, Folder 28)
  - Michales, Mark Edward, 2013 (Box 15, Folder 29)
  - Miller, Thomas Abraham, 2013 (Box 15, Folder 30)
  - Mingo, Tonquan Kyshum, 2013 (Box 15, Folder 31)
  - Morin, Michelle Dee, 2013 (Box 15, Folder 32)
  - Murray, Melissa Renee, 2013 (Box 15, Folder 33)
  - Newcomb, Jonathan Don, 2013 (Box 15, Folder 34)
  - Rivera, Luis Manuel Vesquez, 2013 (Box 15, Folder 35)
  - Robinson, Richard Wayne, 2013 (Box 15, Folder 36)
  - Schoening, Louis Martin, 2013 (Box 15, Folder 37)
  - Sigmon, Curtis J., 2013 (Box 15, Folder 38)
  - Smith, Alan Stanley, 2013 (Box 15, Folder 39)
  - Soliz, Busilio, 2013 (Box 15, Folder 40)
  - Soriano, Juan Fransisco, 2013 (Box 15, Folder 41)
  - Sponaugle, Dennis Wayne, 2013 (Box 15, Folder 42)
  - Staton, Gregory Delmas, 2013 (Box 15, Folder 43)
  - Stevens, Nelson Tyrone, 2013 (Box 15, Folder 44)
  - Stinnett, Thomas Matthew, 2013 (Box 15, Folder 45)
  - Taylor, Antwain Lamont, 2013 (Box 15, Folder 46)
  - Thomas, Gene William, Jr., 2013 (Box 15, Folder 47)
  - Thompson, Sammie David, 2013 (Box 15, Folder 48)
  - Valentine, Monique Lashawn, 2013 (Box 15, Folder 49)
  - Walser, John Lindsay, Jr., 2013 (Box 15, Folder 50)
  - Williams, Cachita R., 2013 (Box 15, Folder 51)
  - Williams, Gregory S., 2013 (Box 15, Folder 52)
  - Williams, Scott, 2013 (Box 15, Folder 53)
  - Woodard, Jonathan Ernest, 2013 (Box 15, Folder 54)
  - Wright, Christopher Hope, 2013 (Box 15, Folder 55)
- Series II: Extraditions Requisitions and Renditions: Requisitions, 2010-2013., Extent: 8 cu. ft. (8 boxes) (Box Boxes 5-12)
  - Adams, Daniel, 2010 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Allen, Chrishon, 2010 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Allison, Melissa Dawn, 2010 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Amaker, Steven, 2010 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Amyx, Gina A., 2010 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Anderson, Michael Terai, 2010 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Anderson, Ralph Clayton, III, 2010 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Andrews, Cheryl Denise, 2010 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Arnold, Elvis Dewayne, 2010 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Arrington, Jamel, 2010 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Arrington, Jamel, 2010 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Badgett, David William, 2010 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Ballance, Jason Lee, 2010 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Ballance, Jason Lee, 2010 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Banks, Derrick Lamont, 2010 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Bayer, Jackie Dee, 2010 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Bauer, Jackie Dee, 2010 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Becker, Charles Robert, 2010 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Benevento, Andrew Blaine, 2010 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Benitez, Carlos A., 2010 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Benson, Joseph James-Cain, 2010 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Bernia-Gonzalez, Geovani, 2010 (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Billingsley, Larry Donell, 2010 (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Bishop, Richard Vance, 2010 (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Broadnax, Michael, 2010 (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - Brinson, Kellam Dior, 2010 (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - Briscoe, Brandon, 2010 (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - Brown-El, Grayling, 2010 (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - Burrell, James Daniel, 2010 (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - Caceres-Villalta, Fernando, 2010 (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - Cameron, John, 2010 (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - Carpenter, John Lewis, 2010 (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - Cavins, Caleb Zane, 2010 (Box 5, Folder 29)
  - Choudhry, Jared, 2010 (Box 5, Folder 30)
  - Clark, August, 2010 (Box 5, Folder 31)
  - Classen, Anthony Richard, 2010 (Box 5, Folder 32)
  - Collins, Hekee DeShawn, 2010 (Box 5, Folder 33)
  - Conner, Anthony, 2010 (Box 5, Folder 34)
  - Cooper, Dean Sharif, 2010 (Box 5, Folder 35)
  - Corrivea, Robert Joseph, 2010 (Box 5, Folder 36)
  - Crangle, James Kent, 2010 (Box 5, Folder 37)
  - Croker, Timothy Terrett, 2010 (Box 5, Folder 38)
  - Darden, Jamel Duval, 2010 (Box 5, Folder 39)
  - Davis, Richard Bradford, III, 2010 (Box 5, Folder 40)
  - Dehart, Jason Robert, 2010 (Box 5, Folder 41)
  - Dehart, Jerry Darrell, 2010 (Box 5, Folder 42)
  - Derring, Lonnell, 2010 (Box 5, Folder 43)
  - Diggs, Corey Edwards, 2010 (Box 5, Folder 44)
  - Doss, Charles Anthony, 2010 (Box 5, Folder 45)